Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXXII is arranged in 49 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXXII. STATE LEGISLATIVE COMMITTEES
  - Sub-Series 429-0. State Legislative Committees
    - General, 1951-1959 (Box 584, Folder 45)
      November 1951-59.
    - General, 1948-1951 (Box 584, Folder 46)
      August 1948-October 1951.
    - General, 1945-1948 (Box 585, Folder 1)
      1945-July 1948.
    - General. National Conference of State Legislative Chairmen, 1955-1956 (Box 585, Folder 2)
    - General. Uniform Per Capita Tax Report, 1951-1956 (Box 585, Folder 3)
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 585, Folder 4)
    - General, 1955-1959 (Box 585, Folder 5)
      November 1955-59.
    - General, 1953-1955 (Box 585, Folder 6)
      October 1953-October 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-1. State Legislative Committees. Alabama.
    - Alabama State Legislative Committee, 1949-1958 (Box 585, Folder 7)
    - Alabama State Legislative Committee, 1945-1948 (Box 585, Folder 8)
    - Alabama State Legislative Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 585, Folder 9)
      August 1960-63.
    - Alabama State Legislative Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 585, Folder 10)
      1957 July 1960.
    - Alabama State Legislative Committee, 1953-1956 (Box 585, Folder 11)
      May 1953-56.
  - Sub-Series 429-4. State Legislative Committees. Arkansas.
    - Arkansas State Legislative Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 585, Folder 12)
    - Arkansas State Legislative Committee, 1949-1959 (Box 585, Folder 13)
      March 1949-59.
  - Sub-Series 429-5. State Legislative Committees. Arizona.
    - Arizona State Legislative Committee, 1935-1956 (Box 585, Folder 14)
    - Arizona State Legislative Committee, 1957-1962 (Box 586, Folder 1)
      March 1957-62.
    - Arizona State Legislative Committee, 1952-1957 (Box 586, Folder 2)
      1952-February 1957.
  - Sub-Series 429-6. State Legislative Committees. California.
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1948-1958 (Box 586, Folder 3)
      June 1948-58.
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1936-1948 (Box 586, Folder 4)
      1936-May 1948.
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1964 (Box 586, Folder 5)
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1963 (Box 586, Folder 6)
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 586, Folder 7)
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 586, Folder 8)
      July 1958-60.
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 586, Folder 9)
      September 8, 1956-June 1958.
    - California State Legislative Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 586, Folder 10)
      March 1954-September 7, 1956.
  - Sub-Series 429-8. State Legislative Committees. Colorado.
    - Colorado State Legislative Committee, 1945-1956 (Box 586, Folder 11)
    - Colorado State Legislative Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 586, Folder 12)
    - Colorado State Legislative Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 586, Folder 13)
      August 1954-58.
  - Sub-Series 429-9. State Legislative Committees. Connecticut.
    - Connecticut State Legislative Committee, 1945-1958 (Box 586, Folder 14)
    - Connecticut State Legislative Committee, 1951-1962 (Box 586, Folder 15)
      July 1951-62.
  - Sub-Series 429-10. State Legislative Committees. Delaware.
    - Delaware State Legislative Committee, 1947-1959 (Box 587, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 429-12. State Legislative Committees. Florida.
    - Florida State Legislative Committee, 1952-1957 (Box 587, Folder 2)
    - Florida State Legislative Committee, 1945-1951 (Box 587, Folder 3)
    - Florida State Legislative Committee, 1963 (Box 587, Folder 4)
    - Florida State Legislative Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 587, Folder 5)
    - Florida State Legislative Committee, 1955-1959 (Box 587, Folder 6)
      May 1955-59.
    - Florida State Legislative Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 587, Folder 7)
      1953-April 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-13. State Legislative Committees. Georgia.
    - Georgia State Legislative Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 587, Folder 8)
    - Georgia State Legislative Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 587, Folder 9)
    - Georgia State Legislative Committee, 1956-1961 (Box 587, Folder 10)
      April 1956-61.
    - Georgia State Legislative Committee, 1953-1956 (Box 587, Folder 11)
      July 1953-March 1956.
  - Sub-Series 429-14. State Legislative Committees. Idaho.
    - Idaho State Legislative Committee, 1945-1956 (Box 587, Folder 12)
    - Idaho State Legislative Committee, 1949-1962 (Box 587, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 429-15. State Legislative Committees. Illinois.
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1948-1959 (Box 587, Folder 14)
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 587, Folder 15)
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1965 (Box 588, Folder 1)
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1964 (Box 588, Folder 2)
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1963 (Box 588, Folder 3)
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 588, Folder 4)
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 588, Folder 5)
      December 14, 1958-59.
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 588, Folder 6)
      February 1957-December 13, 1958.
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 588, Folder 7)
      1956-January 1957.
    - Illinois State Legislative Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 588, Folder 8)
      December 1954-55.
  - Sub-Series 429-16. State Legislative Committees. Indiana.
    - Indiana State Legislative Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 588, Folder 9)
      July 1960-63.
    - Indiana State Legislative Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 588, Folder 10)
      May 1953-April 1955.
    - Indiana State Legislative Committee, 1945-1958 (Box 588, Folder 11)
    - Indiana State Legislative Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 588, Folder 12)
      May 1955-June 1960.
  - Sub-Series 429-17. State Legislative Committees. Iowa
    - Iowa State Legislative Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 588, Folder 13)
    - Iowa State Legislative Committee, 1954-1959 (Box 588, Folder 14)
      March 1954-59.
  - Sub-Series 429-18. State Legislative Committees. Kansas
    - Kansas State Legislative Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 588, Folder 15)
    - Kansas State Legislative Committee, 1965 (Box 589, Folder 1)
    - Kansas State Legislative Committee, 1964 (Box 589, Folder 2)
    - Kansas State Legislative Committee, 1963 (Box 589, Folder 3)
    - Kansas State Legislative Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 589, Folder 4)
    - Kansas State Legislative Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 589, Folder 5)
      July 1955-58.
    - Kansas State Legislative Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 589, Folder 6)
      1954-June 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-19. State Legislative Committees. Kentucky
    - Kentucky State Legislative Committee, 1951-1959 (Box 589, Folder 7)
    - Kentucky State Legislative Committee, 1957-1962 (Box 589, Folder 8)
      April 1957-62.
    - Kentucky State Legislative Committee, 1953-1957 (Box 589, Folder 9)
      June 1953-March 1957.
  - Sub-Series 429-20. State Legislative Committees. Louisiana
    - Louisiana State Legislative Committee, 1951-1959 (Box 589, Folder 10)
    - Louisiana State Legislative Committee, 1961-1964 (Box 589, Folder 11)
    - Louisiana State Legislative Committee, 1956-1960 (Box 589, Folder 12)
    - Louisiana State Legislative Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 589, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 429-21. State Legislative Committees. Maine
    - Maine State Legislative Committee, 1947-1957 (Box 589, Folder 14)
    - Maine State Legislative Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 589, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 429-23. State Legislative Committees. Maryland
    - Maryland State Legislative Committee, 1944-1958 (Box 589, Folder 16)
    - Maryland State Legislative Committee, 1954-1962 (Box 589, Folder 17)
      April 1954-62.
  - Sub-Series 429-24. State Legislative Committees. Massachusetts
    - Massachusetts State Legislative Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 589, Folder 18)
    - Box No. 590 does not exist or is missing. (Box 590)
    - Massachusetts State Legislative Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 591a, Folder 1)
    - Massachusetts State Legislative Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 591a, Folder 2)
      July 1956-59.
    - Massachusetts State Legislative Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 591a, Folder 3)
      July 1954-June 1956.
  - Sub-Series 429-25. State Legislative Committees. Michigan
    - Michigan State Legislative Committee, 1951-1956 (Box 591a, Folder 4)
    - Michigan State Legislative Committee, 1945-1950 (Box 591a, Folder 5)
    - Michigan State Legislative Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 591a, Folder 6)
      June 1957-October 1960.
    - Michigan State Legislative Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 591a, Folder 7)
      August 1955-May 1957.
    - Michigan State Legislative Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 591a, Folder 8)
      October 1954-July 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-26. State Legislative Committees. Minnesota
    - Minnesota State Legislative Committee, 1949-1959 (Box 591a, Folder 9)
    - Minnesota State Legislative Committee, 1945-1948 (Box 591a, Folder 10)
    - Minnesota State Legislative Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 591a, Folder 11)
    - Minnesota State Legislative Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 591b, Folder 1)
      October 1958-61.
    - Minnesota State Legislative Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 591b, Folder 2)
      July 1955-September 1958.
    - Minnesota State Legislative Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 591b, Folder 3)
      August 1952-June 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-27. State Legislative Committees. Mississippi
    - Mississippi State Legislative Committee, 1948-1958 (Box 591b, Folder 4)
    - Mississippi State Legislative Committee, 1947 (Box 591b, Folder 5)
    - Mississippi State Legislative Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 591b, Folder 6)
    - Mississippi State Legislative Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 591b, Folder 7)
      June 1956-59.
    - Mississippi State Legislative Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 591b, Folder 8)
      February 1955-May 1956.
    - Mississippi State Legislative Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 591b, Folder 9)
      April 1954-January 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-28. State Legislative Committees. Missouri
    - Missouri State Legislative Committee, 1948-1954 (Box 591b, Folder 10)
    - Missouri State Legislative Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 592a, Folder 1)
    - Missouri State Legislative Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 592a, Folder 2)
      April 1960-62.
    - Missouri State Legislative Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 592a, Folder 3)
      1957-March 1960.
    - Missouri State Legislative Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 592a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 429-29. State Legislative Committees. Montana
    - Montana State Legislative Committee, 1936-1958 (Box 592a, Folder 5)
    - Montana State Legislative Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 592a, Folder 6)
      February 1961-63.
    - Montana State Legislative Committee, 1955-1961 (Box 592a, Folder 7)
      1955-January 1961.
  - Sub-Series 429-30. State Legislative Committees. Nebraska
    - Nebraska State Legislative Committee, 1945-1958 (Box 592a, Folder 8)
    - Nebraska State Legislative Committee, 1956-1961 (Box 592a, Folder 9)
      1956-March 1961.
    - Nebraska State Legislative Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 592a, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 429-31. State Legislative Committees. Nevada
    - Nevada State Legislative Committee, 1947-1959 (Box 592a, Folder 11)
    - Nevada State Legislative Committee, 1948-1960 (Box 592b, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 429-34. State Legislative Committees. New Hampshire
    - New Hampshire State Legislative Committee, 1947-1956 (Box 592b, Folder 2)
    - New Hampshire State Legislative Committee, 1949-1957 (Box 592b, Folder 3)
      April 1949-57.
  - Sub-Series 429-35. State Legislative Committees. New Jersey
    - New Jersey State Legislative Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 592b, Folder 4)
    - New Jersey State Legislative Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 592b, Folder 5)
    - New Jersey State Legislative Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 592b, Folder 6)
    - New Jersey State Legislative Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 592b, Folder 7)
      June 1957-59.
    - New Jersey State Legislative Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 592b, Folder 8)
      April 1954-May 1957.
  - Sub-Series 429-36. State Legislative Committees. New Mexico
    - New Mexico State Legislative Committee, 1947-1958 (Box 592b, Folder 9)
    - New Mexico State Legislative Committee, 1952-1960 (Box 592b, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 429-37. State Legislative Committees. New York
    - New York State Legislative Committee, 1953-1959 (Box 592b, Folder 11)
    - New York State Legislative Committee, 1949-1952 (Box 592b, Folder 12)
    - New York State Legislative Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 592b, Folder 13)
      April 1961-62.
    - New York State Legislative Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 592b, Folder 14)
      1958-March 1961.
    - New York State Legislative Committee, 1957 (Box 593a, Folder 1)
      April-December 1957.
    - New York State Legislative Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 593a, Folder 2)
      January 1955-March 1957.
  - Sub-Series 429-38. State Legislative Committees. North Carolina
    - North Carolina State Legislative Committee, 1945-1957 (Box 593a, Folder 3)
    - North Carolina State Legislative Committee, 1961-1965 (Box 593a, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina State Legislative Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 593a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 429-39. State Legislative Committees. North Dakota
    - North Dakota State Legislative Committee, 1947-1959 (Box 593a, Folder 6)
    - North Dakota State Legislative Committee, 1955-1962 (Box 593a, Folder 7)
      March 1955-62.
    - North Dakota State Legislative Committee, 1951-1955 (Box 593a, Folder 8)
      August 1951-February 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-41. State Legislative Committees. Ohio
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1950-1955 (Box 593b, Folder 1)
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1947-1949 (Box 593b, Folder 5)
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1944-1946 (Box 593b, Folder 6)
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1965 (Box 593b, Folder 7)
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1964 (Box 593b, Folder 8)
      July-December 1964.
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 593b, Folder 9)
      1963-June 1964.
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1962 (Box 593b, Folder 10)
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 593b, Folder 11)
      September 1960-61.
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 593b, Folder 12)
      August 1959-August 1960.
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 594a, Folder 1)
      October 1956-July 1959.
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 594a, Folder 2)
      March 1955-September 1956.
    - Ohio State Legislative Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 594a, Folder 3)
      November 1954-February 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-42. State Legislative Committees. Oklahoma
    - Oklahoma State Legislative Committee, 1945-1959 (Box 594a, Folder 4)
    - Oklahoma State Legislative Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 594a, Folder 5)
      1961-November 1962.
    - Oklahoma State Legislative Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 594a, Folder 6)
      February 1955-60.
    - Oklahoma State Legislative Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 594a, Folder 7)
      March 1953-January 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-43. State Legislative Committees. Oregon
    - Oregon State Legislative Committee, 1932-1956 (Box 594a, Folder 8)
    - Oregon State Legislative Committee, 1953-1962 (Box 594a, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 429-44. State Legislative Committees. Pennsylvania
    - Pennsylvania State Legislative Committee, 1951-1959 (Box 594a, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania State Legislative Committee, 1945-1950 (Box 594b, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania State Legislative Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 594b, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania State Legislative Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 594b, Folder 3)
      June 1960-62.
    - Pennsylvania State Legislative Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 594b, Folder 4)
      1958-May 1960.
    - Pennsylvania State Legislative Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 594b, Folder 5)
      July 1956-57.
    - Pennsylvania State Legislative Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 594b, Folder 6)
      March 1954-June 1956.
  - Sub-Series 429-46. State Legislative Committees. Rhode Island
    - Rhode Island State Legislative Committee, 1947-1954 (Box 594b, Folder 7)
    - Rhode Island State Legislative Committee, 1951-1962 (Box 594b, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 429-47. State Legislative Committees. South Carolina
    - South Carolina State Legislative Committee, 1947-1953 (Box 594b, Folder 9)
    - South Carolina State Legislative Committee, 1957-1964 (Box 594b, Folder 10)
    - South Carolina State Legislative Committee, 1949-1956 (Box 594b, Folder 11)
      October 1949-56.
  - Sub-Series 429-48. State Legislative Committees. South Dakota
    - South Dakota State Legislative Committee, 1947-1957 (Box 595a, Folder 1)
    - South Dakota State Legislative Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 595a, Folder 2)
    - South Dakota State Legislative Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 595a, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 429-49. State Legislative Committees. Tennessee
    - Tennessee State Legislative Committee, 1945-1956 (Box 595a, Folder 4)
    - Tennessee State Legislative Committee, 1961-1965 (Box 595a, Folder 5)
    - Tennessee State Legislative Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 595a, Folder 6)
      July 6, 1958-60.
    - Tennessee State Legislative Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 595a, Folder 7)
      1955-July 5, 1958.
  - Sub-Series 429-50. State Legislative Committees. Texas
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 595a, Folder 8)
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1963 (Box 595a, Folder 9)
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1962 (Box 595a, Folder 10)
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 595a, Folder 11)
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 595a, Folder 12)
      November 1957-59.
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1955-1957 (Box 595a, Folder 13)
      October 1955-October 1957.
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1950-1958 (Box 595b, Folder 1)
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1944-1949 (Box 595b, Folder 2)
    - Texas State Legislative Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 595b, Folder 3)
      July 1954-September 1955.
  - Sub-Series 429-51. State Legislative Committees. Utah
    - Utah State Legislative Committee, 1945-1958 (Box 595b, Folder 4)
    - Utah State Legislative Committee, 1956-1962 (Box 595b, Folder 5)
    - Utah State Legislative Committee, 1951-1955 (Box 595b, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 429-52. State Legislative Committees. Vermont
    - Vermont State Legislative Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 595b, Folder 7)
    - Vermont State Legislative Committee, 1954-1958 (Box 595b, Folder 8)
      March 1954-58.
    - Vermont State Legislative Committee, 1947 (Box 595b, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 429-53. State Legislative Committees. Virginia
    - Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 595b, Folder 10)
    - Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1957-1959 (Box 595b, Folder 11)
    - Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 596a, Folder 1)
      1955-December 1956.
    - Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1946-1956 (Box 596a, Folder 2)
      June 1946-56.
    - Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 596a, Folder 3)
      1945-May 1946.
    - Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1963 (Box 596a, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 429-54. State Legislative Committees. Washington
    - Washington State Legislative Committee, 1936-1959 (Box 596a, Folder 5)
    - Washington State Legislative Committee, 1958-1963 (Box 596a, Folder 6)
    - Washington State Legislative Committee, 1954-1957 (Box 596a, Folder 7)
      November 1954-57.
    - Washington State Legislative Committee, 1945-1951 (Box 596a, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 429-55. State Legislative Committees. West Virginia
    - West Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1952-1959 (Box 596a, Folder 9)
    - West Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 596b, Folder 1)
    - West Virginia State Legislative Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 596b, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 429-56. State Legislative Committees. Wisconsin
    - Wisconsin State Legislative Committee, 1936-1958 (Box 596b, Folder 3)
    - Wisconsin State Legislative Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 596b, Folder 4)
    - Wisconsin State Legislative Committee, 1958-1962 (Box 596b, Folder 5)
      April 1958-62.
    - Wisconsin State Legislative Committee, 1956-1958 (Box 596b, Folder 6)
      June 1956-March 1958.
    - Wisconsin State Legislative Committee, 1954-1956 (Box 596b, Folder 7)
      March 5, 1954-May 1956.
  - Sub-Series 429-57. State Legislative Committees. Wyoming
    - Wyoming State Legislative Committee, 1951-1959 (Box 596b, Folder 8)
    - Wyoming State Legislative Committee, 1953-1957 (Box 596b, Folder 9)
      September 1953-57.